(Sheldon:)I wonder how he'd feel
(Sheldon:)about taking
the smaller bedroom.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
Hey.
(Bernadette:)You know who would be
the perfect roommate?
(Sheldon:)Gandalf, but he's a smoker.
(Bernadette:)Stuart.
(Bernadette:)He's been living with us
for a while now.
(Bernadette:)I'm sure he'd love
to get us out of his hair.
(Stuart:)Nope, couldn't be happier.
(Bernadette:)Well, Sheldon's looking
for a...
(Stuart:)Nope.
(Bernadette:)He'll think about it.
No I won't!
(Raj:)Have you seen
this Archie comic?
(Raj:)It's actually
Archie versus Predator.
(Howard:)How could Archie
defeat Predator?
(Raj:)I don't know.
(Raj:)Maybe Jughead's a Terminator.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
Hey, Stuart.
(Stuart:)Do you guys know any musicians?
(Howard:)Why?
(Stuart:)I was thinking it might be cool
(Stuart:)to have live music here
a few nights a week.
(Stuart:)You know, give
this place more
of a "staying in business" vibe.
(Howard:)What kind of music
are you thinking of?
(Stuart:)I like all kinds of music,
but my favorite genre is free.